We create book model. Let's now have it in dividing multiple categories.
And now I will just ask about what this needed probably they were asking for icons and multiple things.
So I will just ask how open your agent and now I switch between mode control comma and now we'll just need it to publish this.
I'm a little Chrome web store.
All right, probably obviously we need icons, but any time I want to have two features.
I want to have a possible team.
Now if I go back it's there, so it's great, so you can quickly remove or add something.
We need another thing to keep it open, maybe inside panel.
We can ask for it, maybe I'll ask in the question so go to requirements.
Maybe I will just ask another question but I will keep it.
Okay, great. Please create all of it and adjust hierarchy.
I will add it manually and then we'll create a new agent.
So this is the manifest JSON.
Now just ask again, this control comma and now I switch to ask.
I want to have a possible to keep it open, maybe inside panel.
We need to keep by stick it, open to a side panel.
All right, we can keep this way.
Now we'll actually open it up.
Let me see if I can do it.
If you don't creating it, so we can use it.
The side panel function and we have another one.
This is the requirement so it's creating and the way it's creating, I will go to maybe
ChagibiD and I will use create a little bit type for Chrome extension that will have
us with OSINT.
I will go should be with Bookmark icon and social media with the style.
It's now just created, we'll use Chrome dashboard, I think.
So in the one of the previous videos, I'll show you how we can use almost all the time
they asked me for verification, so I'll put to do it.
And here we see the items.
This is just not for archive, but obviously we can turn off this my account.
I created an account in one of the previous videos, this is my public ID.
As we can see, this is public already.
So it automatically is visible and obviously some of the statistics basically there.
So if I see in stores or only stores, it will be displayed because, but for now, nothing
gets displayed.
So obviously I have to do some more, actually the ID and receive any emails, so I didn't
know it's displayed, but I don't need to eat an item soon.
So first we need to obviously create a CRX file or zip file that will help us.
So first it will just create a logger type, in the meantime we can go back to our, okay,
it's creating a bookmark mark here for Instagram Stories, that's good, this is the requirement,
I'll go on and open the extension, I can refresh it soon, okay, let me refresh, okay,
if I do the extension, now we cannot because you have to add the icon.
So I will go to one of my tools, free online tools and there's like some of the tools
that I really use often, I think it's a free image resizer, I'll use free image resizer,
and after it's created we will go to it, okay, but I would like to have it more as a square,
so obviously I can download as it is, and then open the image that I have downloaded,
I'll go to the nodes and now I have all sent, and now I can just adjust sizes, but if
I go basically to my extension, in icons, we select a pop-ups and scripts, so on the
scripts, 128, 128, I will just use this one, 128, 128, but I will not keep it, so on, let
me see, so the problem is that it's not as square-ish, so we can try to use like a
recraft, they have multiple types, it's another example, so we have a go-up and need a
one, so it's creating something, but it's easier like to create some icon with the titles,
we can even remove a text, so if I tap like text, prep, and the logo, and now I will
just change the width and height, 128, 128, I will just generate it again, this one I like
it too, we can also use it the new way to see how it's in generative, I have to zoom
it out, oh I love it, actually I love it, we can even add some background to it if you want
to, but I think from now it's very great, oh yeah, if you want to remove it, so I will
use the previous one, and when I have an extension, now I can go to Recizer, I will use
this one, and now I will just resize to the size that I want, we didn't need to take
my namespace ratio, because obviously we will not actually need it, because it's already
rectangle, is able to specify it, it's in before, so 128, 48 and 16, I go to Recizer,
this is 128, I will remove all of it, and I will just 48, and now we go back again and
to 16, it's really very small, but actually maybe we can use the more, the full one or
better quality, just in case, so use the first, and now we will use 16, yeah, and I will
just don't know it, so now we have all of it, hold on on the resize, and now obviously
we cannot leave it in the normal naming conversion, as we can see here, so we need to add
proper conversion for naming conversion for it, so we see the references, and icon 16,
there are some even tools that show us that we can use, okay, there's some privacy policy,
I will remove one of the prompts, so first I will obviously need to adjust the PNG, so
and we can use it like icon 48, icon 60, and now icon 128, I will just go to Bookmark, let
again, to one of my Chrome extension, so basically I can even go to here, reviewing the
file explorer, and while I'm here, and icons, I will just press this, and now when I have
it, I will just try to test, so now I can just go and ask, okay, it's working, but we see
that there is a private policy, that we will need, and I will have to generate that private
policy, in one of the videos I show you how we can use it, when I'm here, and I can use
towns, fit for generating for our Chrome extension, and in the meantime, we see when I have
it, so I can ask to remove all of the things, I can read me files, I'm privacy model,
but first I will just generate it, so I got a new agent that will help me, so there is
a terms, and now we can just specify, what is it exactly, this is return from policy, but
we need privacy policy generator, and now we have to go with all of the bookmarks, it will
be like, privacy policy map, what is your map, and I can say, we can switch the name as
well, book, mark, let's ask it, let me look if it's actually correct, okay, okay,
and I will see I'm in the visual, and I will enter a country, I'm from Poland, I will use
the next step, here we can apply, if you press others, you can push them with your
color, because they will not collect anything, and they show ads, no, you send emails
to users, no, no, we don't use anything, but as you can see, if you want to generate it,
you ask it to give you some money, so we can just use default options, now we now sell
data, and nothing, we don't need this, we don't need this, this is not useful, I can
just type email, oh, place my new, and that's pretty neat, and now I can just try, if I
can go to the next step, okay, others, and we have possibly added something, okay, now
just add an agent, later, use this as a policy link, as a prior policy link, given
in the link, and how does the one feature that I haven't tested yet, so my bookmarks
will be hosted, it's a, and you see it now, it's here, and please add me on the
author, that my name, and center it, and to update our manifest file,
go to my extension, refresh, it's looking now great, I think it's better to not have
a bookmarks, and now I can just ask him to remove, remove all unnecessary files, including
it, I'm not like downs, etc, so just leave like a code with the bookmarks, JSON, the
scripts that we have, and the pop-up code that we have basically here, and the scripts
that we used, and now we will remove all of the files that we don't need, okay, and whenever
it's ready, now I can go to reveal it, so I can go here, see the folder, so now when
I am here, I can just go to remove an explorer, and now I have bookmarks, let's all
send, what I'm going to do, obviously, I love my private policy, so I can copy this to
bookmarklessosint, and what I'm going to do, I will just copy it, oh, I cannot, but okay,
I will just add us a new one, so first we need to obviously create a zip file, so whenever
I think it's done, now I'm going to file explorer, and I will just add it to a zip file,
so this is my zip file, and I will create a zip, bookmarklessosint, it's 85 kilobytes, and
I will select a file, go to Chrome extension, bookmarklessosint, add it, the first to be checked,
so there is an initial check from Chrome Web Store, and after I add it, I can select
some of the interesting information, but as you can see, there is like additional fits,
I already done it, and obviously I will need a single purpose privacy, that is required
some justification, we will filter, but remove it, we need privacy, you will see, so the
privacy policy URL, I will use the one that obviously I have here, I created, so I will
just use privacy policy, and go back to, and now I can save draft, and in the very next
video we will just polish some of the things, change the logo type, fit it out, and publish
the Chrome Web Store.